reboundalert.com 2013-04-06

# ReboundAlert - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of the ReboundAlert App and the Site. This Privacy Policy describes the Company's collection and use of users' personal information and non-personally identifiable information. ReboundAlert app should only be installed by users that are of the age of 18 or older. Users under the age of 18 should ask for parental/guardian approval.

### Collection of Information

#### User Submitted Information

Users are not required to create an account or register to use ReboundAlert App. However, when contacting us for issues related to the ReboundAlert App, you may submit personal information to allow us to effectively respond to your inquiry or request.

#### Collected Information

When users access or use the ReboundAlert App, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected, stored and used for business and marketing purposes. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation: IP address, unique identifier number, operating system, browser and other software information, webpage URLs visited, and search queries entered. This collected data may also be supplemented with information obtained from third parties.

We use cookies to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and to better understand our users, which allow us to enhance your experience at the Site. This data may include storing user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, average time spent on pages, features used, and other information which help us determine which features are most important to you and working effectively. If you do not want the Site to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a website tries to put a cookie in your browser software. If you choose to decline cookies, however, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site and it may affect your ability to use some of the services at the Site. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set.

Third parties that support ReboundAlert App by serving advertisements may also use cookies and other tracking technologies described above to collect similar information. The Company does not control these third parties and their use of these technologies is governed by the privacy policies of the third parties using such technologies.

### Use & Disclosure of Information

Information collected from and about users may be used for the following purposes:

We use the information collected to deliver the ReboundAlert App to you, to measure and improve the ReboundAlert App, to personalize your experience by delivering applicable content and advertising, and to provide you with customer support. We may use aggregated or anonymous data about use of and activity on the ReboundAlert App to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the ReboundAlert App. The Company may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors or agents, who help us manage or provide the ReboundAlert App. Such examples of ReboundAlert App include, without limitation: advertising and marketing, developing or supporting products and functionalities, and processing data or statistics. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to the Company.

We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the ReboundAlert App through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you use the ReboundAlert App. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We may share anonymous, non- personally identifiable or aggregated information with third parties to improve the relevancy of the ads you see using the ReboundAlert App. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.

There may be instances when the Company may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Company has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Company, our affiliated companies or their employees, agents and contractors (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the ReboundAlert App; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

### Notice and Modifications

When ReboundAlert has new added functionality to the app, we will provide a notice to you and what upgrades are available. We will not implement the upgrades until you have consented. If you do not want the upgrades, we will provide you with an option to uninstall.

#### Legacy Users

From time-to-time the services will go through compliance testing and certification with third-party online privacy solutions providers. The certification process will only affect legacy users. Legacy users are users that installed the services before the certification date of the services. The services will offer the legacy users within 6 months of the certification date a chance to re-opt and will completely re-opt in legacy users within 1 year. Users who decline will be offered uninstall instructions.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children or collect data from anyone under the age of 13.

### User Control and Uninstalling Software

To uninstall from any of the supported browsers go to the Windows Start Menu and then to Control Panel. Under programs click on uninstall a program. Navigate and click on ReboundAlert. Click on Uninstall/Change.

For more detailed uninstall instructions, feel free to visit the uninstall section on our About page.

### Questions and Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy or its implementation, please email us at [support@reboundalert.com](mailto:support@reboundalert.com).
